J HAN AYE

BACHELORS OF TECHNOLOGY MAJOR





jaeehan@gmail.com



jaeehan.github.io



Vancouver, B.C.

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING

- Java
- Python
- JavaScript/CSS

DATABASE

MySQL

TOOLS

INTEGRATED DEVELOPMENT ENVIRONMENT

- IntelliJ
- PyCharm
- Eclipse
- Visual Studio

WORKFLOW

- Git
- Agile/Scrum
- UML
- REST API

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

Kwantlen Polytechnic University
Dec 2022

PYTHON BOOTCAMP FROM ZERO TO HERO BY JOSE PORTILLA

Udemy Course

Mar 2021

PROFILE

Bachelors of Technology student with strong analytical, communication, organizational, and teamwork skills through 5+ years of research and sales experience. Great understanding of programming, data structures, algorithms, and recursive functions through courses and personal projects.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

MAZE PATH FINDER

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

- Generate the shortest route in a given maze by using the breadthfirst-search algorithm
- Technologies: Python, PyCharm IDE

REACT PERSONAL WEBSITE

May 2021 - Jul 2021

- Deployed and hosted the React application through GitHub pages
- Designed the website to maximize functionality and maintain simplicity
- Technologies: React, CSS, JavaScript, Visual Studio Code, GitHub

SNAKE GAME

Jan 2021 - Apr 2021

- Implemented graphical interfaces using Swing and AWT
- · Brainstormed game concepts and design elements
- Technologies: Java, IntelliJ IDE

GUESS THE WORD GAME

Aug 2020 - Sep 2020

- Gained better understanding of game development through testing and fixing errors
- Technologies: Python, Pycharm IDE

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

SALES ASSOCIATE, EYESTAR OPTICAL

Nov 2019 - Apr 2021

- Supported company mission while providing a positive store culture
- Educated customers about suitable prescription lenses options

SALES ASSOCIATE, ZERO TIME ACCESSORIES

Apr 2014 - Dec 2016

- · Helped build company website using Wix
- Designed UI/UX interface and developed webpages